https://www.sanmarcocoffee.com/privacy-policy.html

Contact Us
0$0.00Your Shopping Cart is empty.
Privacy Policy
San Marco Coffee reserves the right to make changes to this site and our Privacy Policy at any time without notice.
Privacy PolicySan Marco Coffee is committed to protecting your privacy at all times, in all situations. The information we collect about you when you create an account or place and order on SanMarcoCoffee.com is used to process and fulfill your orders and to provide a more personalized experience on our site. SanMarcoCoffee.com uses a GeoTrust secure encrypted TLS connection to increase the security of your information. When you place an order or create an account on our site, we ask you to fill out a form that requests your name, address, email and phone.
We as well sometimes ask for some demographic information such as gender and date of birth.
Your name and address information is used solely to process and fulfill your orders. We will NEVER sell, give, rent or trade this information to others for purposes other than order fulfillment.
Our Use of Log FilesWhen you visit our site we automatically log your IP address, your browser type and your access times. We utilize this information to conduct site performance evaluations, to see where visitors are coming from and to keep track of click stream data (the screens our users visit on our site). This data helps us to determine what content our customers find most appealing so that we can maximize your enjoyment of the site. Log files are not tied to personally identifiable information.
Links To Other SitesThis website may contains links to other sites. Please note that when you click on one of these links, you may be leaving SanMarcoCoffee.com and entering another website. These sites may independently collect or request information about you and we encourage you to read the privacy statements of these linked sites as their privacy policy may differ from ours.
Receiving EmailFrom time to time we may send out email messages alerting you that products are available, to remind you about providing feedback or for promotional offers. In addition, you will receive communication from us 1) if you contact us for a particular reason, 2) order fulfillment, or 3) we need to contact you for administrative purposes.
Legal DisclaimerThough we make every effort to preserve user privacy, we may need to disclose personal information when required by law wherein we have a good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with a current judicial proceeding, a court order or legal process served on this website.
SupplementationWe may correct or supplement your address information with standardized postal representation in order to ensure that your orders are delivered. We do this since we want to make sure that our customers receive their orders and to lower costs associated with shipping carriers.
Our Use of CookiesCookies are pieces of information stored on your computer's hard drive through your Web browser to enable our systems to recognize your browser and to provide features such as storage of items in your Shopping Cart between visits. Please note that cookies from SanMarcoCoffee.com allow you to take advantage of some of our essential features, we recommend that you leave them turned on. For instance, if you block or otherwise reject our cookies, you may not be able to complete a purchase in our store.
Copyright and TrademarksAll content included on this site, including the site design, text, artwork, logos, graphics, icons, and images, are the sole property of San Marco Coffee Inc. and is protected by United States and international copyright laws and other proprietary (including but not limited to intellectual property) rights. ALL RIGHTS RESERVED
Google AnalyticsThe Google Analytics features implemented is based on Display Advertising (e.g., Remarketing, Google Display Network Impression Reporting, the DoubleClick Campaign Manager integration, or Google Analytics Demographics and Interest Reporting). Using the Ads Settings, you can opt-out of Google Analytics for Display Advertising and customize Google Display Network ads. You may also download and install the following Opt-out Browser Add-on by Google Analytics .
Your Feedback is Always WelcomeIf you have any comments and or questions about our privacy policy please
Contact Us.
Categories
Espresso CoffeeSan Marco EspressoGourmet CoffeeGourmet Coffee 1 lbGourmet Coffee 5 lbLimited Time OnlyFlavored CoffeeFlavored Coffee 8 ozFlavored Coffee 1 lbFlavored Coffee 5 lbSingle-Serve CupsGourmet Fresh CupsFlavored Fresh CupsWholesale CoffeeEquipmentEspresso Machine PartsLa Spaziale PartsReseller SuppliesAccessoriesBarista SuppliesCleaning & MaintenanceTableWarePaper BagsPaper FiltersServicesQuoted Products
Information
Order Tracking
About Us
Our Coffee
Ordering & Shipping
Quantity Discounts
Roasting Plant
General FAQ
Have you seen ...
© 2006-2020 SanMarcoCoffee.com All Rights Reserved.
Back to Top
